# Kinjal Bhatt

bhattkinjal.96@gmail.com +1 (226) 975-3161 403 McKay Avenue Windsor, Ontario

## Summary

Work oriented Software QA with overall 2.5 years of experience in manual testing environment and 8 months experience in Implementation Analyst along with the QA - testing. Easily collaborate and communicate with developers and project leaders. Solid history in Bug Finding and good/excellent observations. Willingness to grow more flexible along with the organization. Easily adapt new technologies and adjustable in every work environment. Having confident and professional communication skills. Passionate to learn such things and explore new places.

## **Employment History**

## **Software QA Tester**

Krishna Infotech • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

11/2019 - 05/2021

Worked as an Software Manual tester. Whereas, handled multiple tasks like manual testing, work management, time management, client communication, follow ups on the tasks and reported bugs, gave training to new employee on product/project and it's functionality. Submit daily report. Worked on multiple projects.

# **Implementation Analyst**

Infostretch Corporation (India) Pvt. Ltd. • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

02/2019 - 10/2019

Worked in the project of third party risk management whereas implementing the business ideas and configure the workflow/process as per the client's requirenment. Analyse the requirenments and give a better and efficient solution to configure the process. Took follow ups on queries. Tested existing and/or upcoming features with the help of road map instructions, had communication with developers regarding same and also reported issues, also looked for follow ups.

- Implement the business ideas as per the client's requirement and create business flow chart by using various configuration tools
- Generate bug/issues report and daily submission of work report
- Test case writing, Test Strategy, Documentation
- Regression, Smoke and Ad-hoc testing

## Software QA

Lodestone Software Service Pvt. Ltd. • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

08/2017 - 02/2019

Worked in the project of 'Free Basics Services', which is a 'Facebook' project and organized by 'internet.org'. 'Free Basics Services' project provide a free internet to users with variety of data values (in MB). Perfomed 'Manual testing' in respect to both 'Functional' and 'Non-functional' areas. Reported the issues and handled it personally, whether in the terms of communication or any queries. Follwed-up the tasks (bugs, roadmap) and took actions regarding the behaviors. Last but not the least, I received appreciation number of time from the on-site member and my team mates, as I have a very eye-catching personality to filter out the quality, also I am very creative as able to think out of the box.

- Created 'Test cases' and implemented in sanity, Test Strategy, Documentation,
  Client communication, Report the bugs. Performed Sanity, Regression, Existing
  feature, New Feature (Alpha phase), Ad-hoc, Exploratory, Functional, Non-functional
  testing.
- Appreciated for Good/Intelligent observations and bugs affected in live environment.

#### **Professional Skills**

- Business Analysis
- · Microsoft office
- Open Communication
- Time Management

- Customer service
- Software Manual QA
- Process Implementation
- Adaptability

#### **Education**

# **Data Analytics for Business (Pursuing)**

St. Clair College • Windsor, Ontario

• Currently studying in "Data Analytics for Business" course which mainly includes Database, Visulaization and Machine Learning IT concepts. Completed my 1st semester with 4/4 GPA.

# **Bachelor's Degree (Computer Engineering)**

L.D.College of Engineering

Graduated 06/2017

- Participated in 'GTU Techfest'competiotion, in 'Bug-a-thon' technical game, unfortunately
  not became a winner but came at 4th rank and also in Mock GD/PI activity and certified in
  that
- Worked on 'Baby Care: Baby Infant Development & Parenting tips' project in Core PHP with MYSQL. It gives tips for mother during pregnancy and for baby after pregnancy and also provide online shopping.
- Completed with 8.21 CGPA.

# **Diploma (Computer Engineering)**

R.C. Technical Institute

Graduated 06/2014

- Worked on 'e-learning of Professionals courses' project in .net with c# platform using MYSQL.
   It's about to give a solutions to student. It provides various courses, colleges and universities details according to student's previous education and requirements.
- Completed with 8.22 CGPA

## Languages

• English

• Hindi

## **Personal Traits**

Gujarati

- Extraversion abilities
- Quick learner and Active Listener
- Open communication
- · Client handling
- Willingness to learn and adapt new things/technology

## Work Day Availablity

Available to work on weekdays and weekends as a Full Time.